class DummyData {
  static const Map<String, dynamic> dummyData = {
    'data': [
      {
        'id': 1,
        'user_full_name': 'Daniel Liman',
        'user_major': 'Ilmu Komputer',
        'user_generation': '2023',
        'tags': 'Struktur Data dan Algoritma',
        'question': 'Bagaimana cara menyelesaikan soal nomor 3?',
        'likes': 10,
        'answers': 5,
        'created_at': 1722123421,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 2,
        'user_full_name': 'Rafie Asadel Tarigan',
        'user_major': 'Sistem Informasi',
        'user_generation': '2023',
        'tags': 'Struktur Data dan Algoritma',
        'question': 'Tips daftar jadi asdos? hehe 😭',
        'likes': 214,
        'answers': 40,
        'created_at': 1720155450,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 3,
        'user_full_name': 'Adrian Hamzah',
        'user_major': 'Ilmu Komputer',
        'user_generation': '2022',
        'tags': 'Dasar - Dasar Pemrograman 1',
        'question': 'Ternyata python juga ada batasannya ya',
        'likes': 3455,
        'answers': 223,
        'created_at': 1705173240,
        'attachment_url':
            'https://drive.google.com/uc?export=view&id=1riQsTtYoh6plVVfPBENiH6wSGdl5hXbE',
      },
      {
        'id': 4,
        'user_full_name': 'Budi',
        'user_major': 'Sistem Informasi',
        'user_generation': '2024',
        'tags': 'Matematika Diskret 1',
        'question':
            'Saya ga takut matematika diskret, matematika diskret yang takut sama saya',
        'likes': 10034,
        'answers': 883,
        'created_at': 1752172881,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 5,
        'user_full_name':
            'Bambang Suherman Putra Laksono Maharaja Yang Punya Nama Yang Sangat Panjang',
        'user_major': 'Sistem Informasi',
        'user_generation': '2020',
        'tags': 'Kalkulus 1',
        'question':
            'Kalkulus kok susah ya, padahal cuma turunan dan integral. Ada yang bisa bantu ajarin saya sampai paham?',
        'likes': 110,
        'answers': 40,
        'created_at': 1708355326,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 6,
        'user_full_name': 'Kira Yoshikage',
        'user_major': 'Ilmu Komputer',
        'user_generation': '2016',
        'tags': 'Mewing',
        'question':
            "My name is Yoshikage Kira. I'm 33 years old. My house is in the northeast section of Morioh, where all the villas are, and I am not married. I work as an employee for the Kame Yu department stores, and I get home every day by 8 PM at the latest. I don't smoke, but I occasionally drink. I'm in bed by 11 PM, and make sure I get eight hours of sleep, no matter what. After having a glass of warm milk and doing about twenty minutes of stretches before going to bed, I usually have no problems sleeping until morning. Just like a baby, I wake up without any fatigue or stress in the morning. I was told there were no issues at my last check-up. I'm trying to explain that I'm a person who wishes to live a very quiet life. I take care not to trouble myself with any enemies, like winning and losing, that would cause me to lose sleep at night. That is how I deal with society, and I know that is what brings me happiness. Although, if I were to fight I wouldn't lose to anyone.",
        'likes': 101203,
        'answers': 10,
        'created_at': 1714782171,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 7,
        'user_full_name': 'Skibidi Sigma Rizz Gyatt',
        'user_major': 'Ilmu Komputer',
        'user_generation': '2021',
        'tags': 'On Skibidi',
        'question':
            'Bro thought he could become the next rizz king by doing the uncanny ankha zone dance like a sussy baka in ohio💀dont bro know quandale dingle already did the forgis on the jeep thug shaker banban style with baller💀bro aint ever making it out of oklahoma the ocky way💀 that shit just plain uncanny like skibidi toilet bro💀 bro got negative infinity morbin chill bill pizza tower barbenheimer rizz bro💀bro got that nathaniel b ahh griddy bro💀bro really thought he had that rise of gru grimace shake 1 2 buckle my shoe spiderverse whopper rizz bro💀bro got that canon event baby gronk waffle house monday left me broken ahh drip in ohio bro💀 we aint ever makin it out of ohio with bros goofy ahh dj khaled mr chedda sisyphus toxic gossip train pikmin 4 ahh rizz bro💀 that aint even elephant mario titanic submarine god tier rizz bro💀thats just uncanny like shadow wizard money gang ambatukam twitter x bro💀fr bro💀',
        'likes': 12200,
        'answers': 110,
        'created_at': 1708320679,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 8,
        'user_full_name': 'Abang Ganteng',
        'user_major': 'Sistem Informasi',
        'user_generation': '2011',
        'tags': 'Pengantar Organisasi Komputer',
        'question': 'Yang ngajar POK tahun 2025 siapa sih?',
        'likes': 100,
        'answers': 10,
        'created_at': 1706305883,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 9,
        'user_full_name': 'Caca Marica',
        'user_major': 'Ilmu Komputer',
        'user_generation': '2022',
        'tags': 'Pengantar Sistem Digital',
        'question': 'Ada yang bikin logisim kayak begini juga gak guys?',
        'likes': 1234,
        'answers': 100,
        'created_at': 1720155450,
        'attachment_url':
            'https://drive.google.com/uc?export=view&id=1UcCsyKAMj8QRJSOhCrbUUkE4yjfWeohD',
      },
      {
        'id': 10,
        'user_full_name': 'Dede',
        'user_major': 'Sistem Informasi',
        'user_generation': '2023',
        'tags': 'Pemrograman Berbasis Platform',
        'question':
            'Kenapa PHP itu jelek? Padahal PHP itu bagus loh, banyak yang pake',
        'likes': 1,
        'answers': 1234,
        'created_at': 1717789895,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 11,
        'user_full_name': 'Eko',
        'user_major': 'Ilmu Komputer',
        'user_generation': '2024',
        'tags': 'Kalkulus 2',
        'question': 'o',
        'likes': 134,
        'answers': 12,
        'created_at': 1720356189,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 12,
        'user_full_name': 'Fajar',
        'user_major': 'Sistem Informasi',
        'user_generation': '2025',
        'tags': 'MPKT',
        'question': 'Kurang ajar yang plagiat, bikin sendiri dong dasar 😡',
        'likes': 123,
        'answers': 1234,
        'created_at': 1711419016,
        'attachment_url':
            'https://drive.google.com/uc?export=view&id=1iG5VS7N6yAyhugfFK5lCQEGmPnMqYgXj',
      },
      {
        'id': 13,
        'user_full_name': 'Gina',
        'user_major': 'Ilmu Komputer',
        'user_generation': '2026',
        'tags': 'Sistem Operasi',
        'question': 'OS tuh gampang kan? Kenapa banyak yang ga lulus?',
        'likes': 12324,
        'answers': 23,
        'created_at': 1722123421,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 14,
        'user_full_name': 'Hadi',
        'user_major': 'Sistem Informasi',
        'user_generation': '2027',
        'tags': 'Tugas Akhir',
        'question': 'TA gw apa bikin konservasi penyu ya? 🐢',
        'likes': 123,
        'answers': 56,
        'created_at': 1713921013,
        'attachment_url':
            'https://drive.google.com/uc?export=view&id=18w_I714EvVzDffMZE6cfM-A-dDPk2Yvw',
      },
      {
        'id': 15,
        'user_full_name': 'Irfan',
        'user_major': 'Ilmu Komputer',
        'user_generation': '2028',
        'tags': 'Basis Data',
        'question':
            'SELECT * FROM mahasiswa WHERE nama = "Irfan" AND kelas = "A"',
        'likes': 1023,
        'answers': 63,
        'created_at': 1707693911,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 16,
        'user_full_name': 'Elon Musk',
        'user_major': 'Sistem Informasi',
        'user_generation': '1994',
        'tags': 'Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak',
        'question':
            'Saya dengar ada aplikasi forum baru, boleh saya beli yang ini juga? 😁',
        'likes': 134,
        'answers': 12,
        'created_at': 1720356189,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 17,
        'user_full_name': 'Joshua Montolalu',
        'user_major': 'Sistem Informasi',
        'user_generation': '2022',
        'tags': 'Pengantar Sistem Digital',
        'question':
            'Apakah basic cylical counter saya sudah benar? Mohon bantuannya',
        'likes': 123,
        'answers': 1234,
        'created_at': 1711419016,
        'attachment_url':
            'https://drive.google.com/uc?export=view&id=1C4cH2IJ8wInB62eZp3KiH6KTZwpA3Hfi',
      },
      {
        'id': 18,
        'user_full_name': '五条 さとる',
        'user_major': 'Ilmu Komputer KKI',
        'user_generation': '2021',
        'tags': 'Foundation of Programming 1 (KKI)',
        'question':
            'ごめんなさい、アマナイさん。私は 今、あなたのことでさえ怒っていませ ん。私は誰に対しても恨みを持ちませ ん。ただ、世界は今、とてもとても素 晴らしいと感じています。「天と地 を通して、私だけが光栄な者です。」 何世代にもわたって受け継がれてきた 技術のメリットは、取扱説明書がある ことです。デメリットとしては、手法 に関する情報が漏洩しやすいことで す。しかし、五条でもこのことを知る 一族はごくわずか。 🔴🔵 増幅と 反転を取得し、それら2つの異なる 無限の表現を組み合わせて、想像上の 塊を作成して押し出します。 空想 技:紫。 🟣',
        'likes': 12324,
        'answers': 23,
        'created_at': 1722123421,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 19,
        'user_full_name': '毛泽东',
        'user_major': 'Ilmu Komputer KKI',
        'user_generation': '2023',
        'tags': 'Introduction to Computer Organization (KKI)',
        'question':
            '动态网自由门 天安門 天安门 法輪功 李洪志 Free Tibet 六四天安門事件 The Tiananmen Square protests of 1989 天安門大屠殺 The Tiananmen Square Massacre 反右派鬥爭 The Anti-Rightist Struggle 大躍進政策 The Great Leap Forward 文化大革命 The Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution 人權 Human Rights 民運 Democratization 自由 Freedom 獨立 Independence 多黨制 Multi-party system 台灣 臺灣 Taiwan Formosa 中華民國 Republic of China 西藏 土伯特 唐古特 Tibet 達賴喇嘛 Dalai Lama 法輪功 Falun Dafa 新疆維吾爾自治區 The Xinjiang Uyghur Autonomous Region 諾貝爾和平獎 Nobel Peace Prize 劉暁波 Liu Xiaobo 民主 言論 思想 反共 反革命 抗議 運動 騷亂 暴亂 騷擾 擾亂 抗暴 平反 維權 示威游行 李洪志 法輪大法 大法弟子 強制斷種 強制堕胎 民族淨化 人體實驗 肅清 胡耀邦 趙紫陽 魏京生 王丹 還政於民 和平演變 激流中國 北京之春 大紀元時報 九評論共産黨 獨裁 專制 壓制 統一 監視 鎮壓 迫害 侵略 掠奪 破壞 拷問 屠殺 活摘器官 誘拐 買賣人口 遊進 走私 毒品 賣淫 春畫 賭博 六合彩 天安門 天安门 法輪功 李洪志 Winnie the Pooh 劉曉波动态网自由门',
        'likes': 123,
        'answers': 56,
        'created_at': 1713921013,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 20,
        'user_full_name': '오징어 게임',
        'user_major': 'Ilmu Komputer KKI',
        'user_generation': '2024',
        'tags': 'Data Structures and Algorithms (KKI)',
        'question': '무궁화 꽃이 피었습니다',
        'likes': 1098723,
        'answers': 63,
        'created_at': 1707693911,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 21,
        'user_full_name': 'Tulus',
        'user_major': 'Ilmu Administrasi Niaga',
        'user_generation': '2022',
        'tags': 'Akuntansi Keuangan',
        'question': 'Anak Pacil kok ada yang ngambil Akuntansi Keuangan?',
        'likes': 134,
        'answers': 12,
        'created_at': 1720356189,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 22,
        'user_full_name': 'Joe Matthew Rusli',
        'user_major': 'Sistem Informasi',
        'user_generation': '2022',
        'tags': 'Aljabar Linear',
        'question': 'Kelas alin gacor cuy dapet haaland nih',
        'likes': 123,
        'answers': 1234,
        'created_at': 1711419016,
        'attachment_url':
            'https://drive.google.com/uc?export=view&id=1ilTDHuZLmfEZkv3qMmyrffEB3eDx1o1U',
      },
      {
        'id': 23,
        'user_full_name': 'Rahardian Reza',
        'user_major': 'Vokasi',
        'user_generation': '2022',
        'tags': 'MPK Bahasa Inggris',
        'question': 'Ada yang mau ditutor bahasa inggris ga?',
        'likes': 12324,
        'answers': 23,
        'created_at': 1722123421,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 24,
        'user_full_name': 'Taylor Swift',
        'user_major': 'Vokasi',
        'user_generation': '1985',
        'tags': 'Tugas Akhir',
        'question': 'Manggung di JGTC enak kali ye',
        'likes': 123,
        'answers': 56,
        'created_at': 1713921013,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
      {
        'id': 25,
        'user_full_name': 'Irfan',
        'user_major': 'Ilmu Komputer',
        'user_generation': '2021',
        'tags': 'Basis Data',
        'question': 'Bikin dummy data capek juga ya mikirnya anjir',
        'likes': 2455,
        'answers': 1122,
        'created_at': 1707693911,
        'attachment_url': null,
      },
    ]
  };
}
